[](https://www.facebook.com/ZAGmotors/)[](https://twitter.com/zagmotors)[](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHGEFIxIvjskgm8ZDTM7CyA)[](https://www.instagram.com/zagmotors/)Directions Icon Created by potrace 1.15, written by Peter Selinger 2001-2017 EVERETT •   13011 Highway 99, Everett, WA 98204   Directions Icon Created by potrace 1.15, written by Peter Selinger 2001-2017 LYNNWOOD •   15431 Highway 99, Lynnwood, WA 98087  

Browse Inventory

Shopping Tools

 Click to return to menu.

* [Get pre-qualified with Capital One (no impact to your credit score)](https://www.zagmotors.com/get-pre-qualified/)

Learn More About Our Dealership

 Click to return to menu.

Smart Search Misc Icon Phone Icon Directions Icon Created by potrace 1.15, written by Peter Selinger 2001-2017

ZAG Motors☰  

* INVENTORY
    * Browse Inventory

    * Shopping Tools

* FINANCE

        * [Get pre-qualified with Capital One (no impact to your credit score)](https://www.zagmotors.com/get-pre-qualified/)
            
* TRADE OR SELL US YOUR CAR

* ABOUT US
    * Learn More About Our Dealership

Close

EVERETT [855-428-7865](wtai://wp/mc;855-428-7865)

LYNNWOOD [888-764-7979](wtai://wp/mc;888-764-7979)

Close

Privacy Policy
==============

Information regarding ZAG Motors's privacy practices:
-----------------------------------------------------

* * *

This document describes ZAG Motors's policy regarding standard information collected in normal web site usage as well as information you provide when you visit our web site. The amount and type of information received depends on how you use our site.

### Normal Web Site Usage:

During normal web site usage, we do not collect or store personally identifiable information such as name, mailing address, e-mail address, phone number, or social security number. You can visit ZAG Motors's web site to read product, company, and other information. The only information we collect and store during normal web site usage is the name of your Internet service provider, the web site you last visited, the pages you request, and the date and time of those requests.We collect this information to generate statistics and measure site activity to improve the usefulness of customer visits. This information is shared only within ZAG Motors.

### Collection of Personal Information:

At times, particularly when you use one of our on-line services (i.e., new-car buying, used-car buying, ZAG Motors's on-line credit application, etc.) ZAG Motors may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to fill out any one of these forms. If you choose to use one of these on-line services, however, ZAG Motors may require that you provide information, which may include your name, mailing address, e-mail address, social security number or other personally identifying information. When you submit personal information to ZAG Motors, you understand and agree that ZAG Motors may access, store, and utilize your customer profile information. We may share information about your personal information with reputable credit reporting agencies as authorized under federal and state laws, but only as lawfully permitted or required. We collect this information for a variety of reasons, including but not limited to informing you of special offers, and other products and services from ZAG Motors.

While we have not done so at this time, in the future we may contract with other reputable companies in our efforts to offer you additional attractive products and services. If you do not want the information you provide to ZAG Motors to be shared with other companies, please indicate this preference when you provide the information to ZAG Motors in the comments section. Of course, we will honor your request.

ZAG Motors's privacy practices are designed to provide a high level of protection for your personal information and our computer systems.

### **Interest-Based/Online Behavioral Advertising:**

On some pages of our site we may allow third-party advertising partners to set web tracking tools (e.g., cookies and web beacons) to collect anonymous, non-personally identifiable information regarding your activities on those pages (e.g., your IP address, page(s) visited, time of day). We may also share such information we have collected with third-party advertising partners. These advertising partners may use this information (and similar information collected from other websites) for purposes of delivering future targeted advertisements to you when you visit other sites within their networks. This practice is commonly referred to as "interest-based advertising" or "online behavioral advertising."

A "cookie" is a small text file or text identifier placed on your computer to assist us in providing customized services. We use cookies to provide you with a convenience feature to save you time and provide a more personalized experience on our site. For example, you may log on once during a visit and will be able to access multiple servers without having to log on again and again. We also use the information for internal research on our user's demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand our visitor's preferences. We may use cookies provided by Google . You have the ability to accept or decline cookies.

* * *

CCPA  
  
INFORMATION COLLECTED

We collect the following categories of information from and about you:

* Contact information, such as name, postal address, email address, and phone number.
* Information regarding your lease or finance terms and monthly payment amounts, that we may obtain from third-party sources.
* Information regarding the mileage on your vehicle, which is collected when you bring your vehicle to our dealership’s service department, or that we may obtain from third-party sources.
* Geolocation information.
* Online identifiers, such as username and IP address.
* Usage information, such as how you and your device interact with our website (e.g., the pages you visit or the search terms you enter).
* Other information, such as your car preferences, or information regarding your potential trade-in vehicle, that you provide or that we may obtain from third-party sources.

COOKIES

We, and third parties we allow, use cookies and other similar technologies. Cookies are small text files placed on your device that uniquely identify your device and which a website can transfer to a consumer’s hard drive to keep records of his or her visit to a website. We, or third parties, may use session cookies or persistent cookies. Session cookies only last for the specific duration of your visit and are deleted when you close your browser. Persistent cookies remain on your device’s hard drive until you delete them or they expire. Different cookies are used to perform different functions, which are explained below:

* Essential. Some cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around our website and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of our website. Without these cookies, we cannot enable appropriate content based on the type of device you are using.
* Analytics. We use Google Analytics to measure how you interact with our website and to improve your user experience. To learn more about Google Analytics privacy practices and opt-out mechanisms, please visit the Google Analytics Security and Privacy Principles page at [https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en.](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en) Google also provides a complete privacy policy and instructions on opting-out of Google Analytics at [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)
* Targeted Advertising. We use cookies to compile information on our users interaction with our website. We use this information to serve ads to you off of our website.

There are several ways to manage cookies. You can control the use of cookies at the browser level, by instructing your browser to accept cookies, disable cookies or notify you when receiving a new cookie. Please note that if you reject cookies, you may still use our website, but your ability to use some features or areas of our website may be limited. The Network Advertising Initiative also offers a means to opt-out of a number of advertising cookies. Please visit www.networkadvertising.org to learn more. Note that opting-out does not mean you will no longer receive online advertising. It does mean that the company or companies from which you opted-out will no longer deliver ads tailored to your preferences and usage patterns.

USE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED

We use the information we collect from you for the following purposes:

* To provide our Services.
* To send you marketing communications.
* To respond to your requests and inquiries.
* To improve user experiences by making our website easier to use and navigate.
* For other legitimate business purposes.

SHARING AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

We may share or disclose your information to the following categories of third parties and for the following reasons:

* To third-party service providers, agents or independent contractors who help us maintain our Services and provide other administrative services to us.
* To unaffiliated third parties whose products and/or services we believe might be of interest to you.
* We may share your personal information in the course of any reorganization process including, but not limited to, mergers, acquisitions, and sales of all or substantially all of our assets.
* We may disclose your personal information to law enforcement, government agencies, and other related third parties, in order to comply with the law, enforce our policies, or protect our or others’ rights, property or safety.

If you would like to see your personal information collected, delete your personal information from our records, opt out of the sale of your personal information or have any questions concerning your personal information please fill out the form on [our CCPA page](https://www.zagmotors.com/personal-consumer-information/) and one of our representatives will reach out to you.

We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy. A revised Privacy Policy will only apply to data collected subsequent to its effective date. Any revisions will be posted at least 10 days prior to its effective date.

Directions Icon Created by potrace 1.15, written by Peter Selinger 2001-2017 EVERETT 13011 Highway 99  
Everett, WA 98204  

Directions Icon Created by potrace 1.15, written by Peter Selinger 2001-2017 LYNNWOOD 15431 Highway 99  
Lynnwood, WA 98087  

LYNNWOOD & EVERETT HOURS

* * Sales Hours
        * Monday 9:15 am - 8:00 pm
        * Tuesday 9:15 am - 8:00 pm
        * Wednesday 9:15 am - 8:00 pm
        * Thursday 9:15 am - 8:00 pm
        * Friday 9:15 am - 8:00 pm
        * Saturday 10:00 am - 8:00 pm
        * Sunday 10:00 am - 7:00 pm
* * Sales Hours
        * Monday 9:15 am - 8:00 pm
        * Tuesday 9:15 am - 8:00 pm
        * Wednesday 9:15 am - 8:00 pm
        * Thursday 9:15 am - 8:00 pm
        * Friday 9:15 am - 8:00 pm
        * Saturday 10:00 am - 8:00 pm
        * Sunday 10:00 am - 7:00 pm

Visit Us on Social Media

[Sitemap](https://www.zagmotors.com/sitemap/)  •  [Privacy Policy](https://www.zagmotors.com/privacy-policy/) This website was designed to perform by [Dealer eProcess](https://www.dealereprocess.com/) © 2024 ZAG Motors. All Rights Reserved.
